<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="backup_address_dialog">
        <item>Backup all</item>
        <item>Only backup changes</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="recovery_address_dialog">
        <item>Restore all</item>
        <item>Only restore changes</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="backupfrequency">
        <item>every_three_hours</item>
        <item>every_day</item>
        <item>every_week</item>
        <item>close_backup</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="backupfrequencyvalue">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="onekeySelectorValues">
        <item>Contacts</item>
        <item>Messages</item>
        <item>CallLogs</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="app_backup_states">
        <item>Waiting</item>
        <item>Backuping</item>
        <item>Backuped</item>
        <item>Error</item>
        <item>OK</item>
        <item>OK</item>
        <item>Canceled</item>
        <item>OK</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="app_regain_states">
        <item>Waiting</item>
        <item>Downloading</item>
        <item>Uninstall</item>
        <item>Error</item>
        <item>Update</item>
        <item>Installed</item>
        <item>Canceled</item>
        <item>Installing</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="more_pager_titles">
        <item>Documents</item>
        <item>SMS</item>
        <item>MMS</item>
        <item>Call Logs</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="frequency_question">
        <item>What’s the default password of LenovoSync? Then how to change the password ? What should I do if I forget my password?</item>
        <item>Dose LenovoSync charge?</item>
        <item>How to manage my backup data when I have backed up completely?</item>
        <item>Are the LenovoSync and Android Backup the same software?</item>
        <item>Is LenovoSync safe? Will it steal my telephone number or my backup data?</item>
        <item>How to log out?</item>
        <item>How to restore my contacts if I have deleted them by mistake?</item>
        <item>Why does my contacts reduce after backup?</item>
        <item>My phone is not made by Lenovo. Can I use LenovoSync?</item>
        <item>Does LenovoSync support other platforms?</item>
        <item>How does work about LenovoSync restoring app?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="frequency_answer">
        <item>"Default Password: You will get a message from Lenovo after your phone automatically registers and login the LenovoSync. Please check whether the kind of Security Software(as LeSecurity Center,360se and so on) obstructs the message or not in case you don’t get it for a long time. If you lose the message or never get it, please refer to ” Forget My Password”. 

\u0009\u0009Change My Password: Visit the website http://cloud.lenovo.com with PC and login. Then go to change. 

\u0009\u0009Forget My Password : Click the [Settings] at the upper-right corner in the LenovoSync. Then choose the [ID Setting].If you have been logged in, please log out. Then click the [Forget Password]."</item>
        <item>LenovoSync is a free mobile APP. But the network traffic cost which is produced by loading and using will be charged by operators.</item>
        <item>Visit the website http://cloud.lenovo.com with PC and login. Then you can operate what data you have backed up, such as delete, modify, add, etc.</item>
        <item>Yes,they are.</item>
        <item>"LenovoSync stores user's information in the way of online banking-level encryption. It can definitely keep the personal data and information security and they will never be leaked."</item>
        <item>Click the [Settings] at the upper-right corner. Then choose the [ID Setting] Click the [Settings] at the upper-right corner or click the menu key and click the [Log Out]</item>
        <item>"If you delete the contacts by your phone, once backed up contacts, you can try to [Recover Contact] through your phone. 

\u0009\u0009If you delete the contacts and backups, your cloud contacts maybe disappear. In this case, please visit the website http://cloud.lenovo.com and login by PC. Check out the [Trash] to recover. After you finish it, please click [Restore Contacts] to make sure your phone’s data kept in touch with the cloud."</item>
        <item>LenovoSync will automatically merge the reduplicated contacts in your phone.</item>
        <item>Of course you can. If your phone’s system is one of the followings: Android, iOS, Symbian or supporting java, you can find the match version to use.</item>
        <item>Yes, it supports Symbian , iOS, Android and Java platform.</item>
        <item>LenovoSync will find latest and best match version.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
